http://www.x-formation.com/company/privacy-statement/

HomeLicensingPresentationTestimonialsWebinarProductsAll productsLicense StatisticsGet trial versionDownloadBenefits and featuresPricingLive demoWebinarsResellersLM-X License ManagerGet trial versionVendor downloadsEnd user downloadsBenefits and featuresPricingWebinarsLicense Activation CenterBenefits and featuresPricingLive demoWebinarsSupportGet supportDocumentationMediaBlogNewsletterYouTubeLinkedInFacebookAbout X-FormationContact usFeedback for the CEOTestimonialsResellersJobsAbout usLast modified on May 24, 2018IntroductionX-Formation Denmark ApS, a limited liability company having its registered office located at Sioevaenget 18, 8381 Tilst, Denmark (“X-Formation”) respects the privacy of each individual that visits our websites or responds to our interactive requests, registration screens and online forms. This Privacy Statement explains what information X-Formation collects about you and why, what we do with that information, how we share it, and how we handle the content you place in our products and services. This Privacy Statement will also instruct you on what to do if you do not want your information collected or shared when you visit the X-Formation website or respond to our advertisements.Scope of the Privacy StatementThis Privacy Statement applies to the information that we obtain through your use of “X-Formation Services” or when you otherwise interact with X-Formation.“X-Formation Services” include our:WebsitesSaaS ProductsDownloadable ProductsChanges to the Privacy StatementX-Formation reserves the right to change, modify, add, or remove portions of this Privacy Statement at any time (for example to reflect updates to the X-Formation Services or to reflect changes in the law). If X-Formation changes this Privacy Statement, we will notify you of these changes by revising the “Last updated” date at the top of this Statement.Information we collect from your use of X-Formation ServicesYou may provide X-Formation with information about you and your company, including your personal information (such as your name, address, telephone number, email address, card number or billing information) as you register for an account, download, make purchases through, use, view, or otherwise interact with the X-Formation Services. X-Formation will not collect any information about you unless you provide to us voluntarily.Information collected automaticallyIn some cases, for example when you access the X-Formation Services or open one of our HTML emails, we may automatically record certain information from your system by using Cookies or other types of tracking technologies. This “automatically collected” information includes but is not limited to: Internet Protocol address (“IP Address”), a unique user ID, device type and identifier, the type of Internet Browser you are using and language, platform type, version of software installed, system type, the content and pages that you access on the X-Formation Services, the number of clicks, the amount of time spent on pages, the dates and times that you visit our websites, the domain name of the website from which you linked to the X-Formation Services, and other similar information. Depending on the law of your country of residence, your IP Address may legally be deemed personal information.Cookies and other tracking technologiesWhen you view our websites or advertisements, we may store some information on your computer. This information will be in the form of a “Cookie” or similar file and will helps us in many ways. For example, Cookies allow us to tailor our websites or advertisements to better match your interests and preferences. With most Internet Browsers, you can erase Cookies from your computer hard drive, block all Cookies, or receive a warning before a Cookie is stored. Please refer to your Browser instructions or help screen to learn more about these functions. We also reserve the right, but do not assume the obligation, to monitor your use of the X-Formation Services. This includes capturing your mouse movements, page transitions, clicks, scrolls, etc. in order to improve your experience with our products and services.How we use information we collectWhen you do provide us with information, we may use that information in the following ways, unless stated otherwise: we may store and process that information to process your order and deliver products you ordered, better understand your needs and how we can improve our products and services; we may use that information to contact you; and we may use that information to let you access limited-entry areas of our website as may be appropriate.Data securityX-Formation uses commercially reasonable security measures to safeguard and protect the your personal information against unauthorized access, accidental loss, improper use and disclosure. However, no security precautions or systems can be completely secure, so we cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to X-Formation, and you do so at your own risk.Data storageAll the personal data we store is deleted periodically and is not stored any longer than necessary. Upon your request, we can remove your personal data or make it available to you for inspection.Data breachWe store your personal data in accordance with EU laws and appropriate data security procedures. In the case of a personal data breach, we shall notify appropriate authorities and affected customers of the breach without undue delay, and where feasible, within 72 hours of discovering a breach, unless the breach is unlikely to result in a risk to the rights and freedoms of persons.Commercial communicationsBy signing up for X-Formation Services you expressly agree to receive commercial communications related to X-Formation Services, including newsletters, emails, offers and promotions. These commercial communications will only be sent by X-Formation. If you do not wish to receive such communications, you may unsubscribe, at any time, by sending an email to the address indicated below or by clicking the “Unsubscribe from this list” link at the bottom of a newsletter you receive from X-Formation.Consent clause for processing of personal data in recruitmentBy sending us your application you agree to the processing of your personal data for recruitment processes by X-Formation Poland Sp. z o. o. located in Krakow at ul. Radzikowskiego 47A, in accordance with the The General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR) (EU) 2016/679.Consent clause for processing of personal data in future recruitmentsBy sending us your application you agree to the processing of your personal data for recruitment processes by X-Formation Poland Sp. z o. o. located in Krakow at ul. Radzikowskiego 47A, in accordance with the The General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR) (EU) 2016/679.ContactIf you do not want your information collected, please do not submit it to us. If you have already submitted this information and would like us to remove it from our records, please contact us at sales@x-formation.com or write at:X-Formation Denmark ApS Sioevaenget 18 8381 Tilst DenmarkWe will use all reasonable efforts to delete your information from our existing files.
We use cookies to ensure that we give you the best experience on our website. If you continue to use this site we will assume that you are happy with it.Ok
